BRENT NICHOLAS

Software Engineer

PROFILE

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science (BSCS) graduate offering a strong foundation in general knowledge programming across multiple platforms. Experienced in Low-level, Object-Oriented and DBMS programming; Experienced in the fundamentals of computer networking and the internet; developing, unit testing and debugaina code; designing interfaces; working alongside team members on sections of code; administering database systems and networks. Strong foundation and experience in source control and quick learner in mastering

CONTACT

technology.

PHONE: 281-979-6871

GITHUB:

https://scor0806.github.io/Brent.Nicholas

new tools, platforms and

EMAIL:

Brentnicholas2011@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Lonestar College System – University Park

August 2012 – May 2014 Associate of Science

University of Houston

August 2015 – December 2019 Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Minor in Mathematics

Courses completed –
Data Structures and Algorithms
Automata and Computability
Operating Systems
Assembly Language Programming
Design File and Database Systems
Computer Networks

WORK EXPERIENCE

[Texas Army National Guard] - Aircraft Pneudraulics Repairer

July 2012 – July 2018
Received Distinguished Service Graduate medal
Army Achievement medal
Completed Basic Leadership Course
Completed Networking Course

[HEB] - [Overnight Stocker]

July 2012 – Present Received Employee of the month in 2015 Worked various departments and all-around worker handling many tasks.

[TECH Projects]

Disclosed Projects – Quantum Leap(Side-Scroller Game-C#.NET, Unity Game Engine), Computer Graphics(C++), Project Management System(Database app-MySQL), Xchange-rate(Android app-Kotlin), Text Editor(Java), Photo Filter App(Python), Calculator(Python)

Ongoing Projects – Flashlight App(Kotlin), Weather App built for Linux and Windows(Python)

TECHNOLOGIES

